<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="info">Info</string>
    <string name="feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="updater">Updater</string>
    <string name="app_name">Quotes</string>
    <string name="editors_choice">Editors Choice</string>
    <string name="samsung_design">Samsung design</string>
    <string name="noInternet">No Internet</string>
    <string name="persons">Persons</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="all_quotes">All quotes</string>
    <string name="update">Update</string>
    <string name="copy_quote">Copy quote</string>
    <string name="share_quote">Share quote</string>
    <string name="options">Options</string>
    <string name="pp">Quotes is a free Android application, made by me, Luca. Quotes does not collect any data and never will. Every interaction with me is selectable. I am offering the possibility of sending me mails, which includes bugs, features and/or feedback. When the conversation with the user has ended, I will delete the contact data and the conversation due to the security of data.\n\nI may change the Privacy Policy. Every change is effective immediately. An information of the change of the Privacy Policy can be found on the changelog\n\nEffective September 3, 2022</string>
    <string name="notes_of_thanks">Note of thanks</string>
    <string name="report_bugs">Report bug</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="request_feature">Suggest feature</string>
    <string name="legal_and_privacy">Legal and Privacy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="app_permissions">App permissions</string>
    <string name="Thanks">I want to say thank you especially to two developers who teach me how to code even though my knowledge was at around 0%. The developers helped me (and still do) even if I never understood anything (and still don\'t :3). So huge thanks, Yanndroid and Tenseventy7!</string>
    <string name="permissions">This app uses some permissions. This page will explain to you why my app needs these permissions.\n\nRead and write storage: The Quotes app needs to be able to read and write to the storage in order to save and install app updates on the device. No data is written to storage.\n\nFull Internet Access: This permission allows my app to get the quotes from my file on the Internet. No data is collected from me.\n\nInstall unknown packages: This permission allows my app to install the update.</string>
    <string name="refreshing">Refreshing… please wait.</string>
    <string name="bugSubject">I found a bug</string>
    <string name="bugMessage">Here\'s what I did while it was happening:\nThis is the bug:</string>
    <string name="feedbackSubject">Here is my feedback</string>
    <string name="feedbackMessage">Hello Luca, I wanted to tell you about my experience with the app</string>
    <string name="suggestionSubject">I have a feature suggestion</string>
    <string name="suggestionMessage">Hi Luca, I was thinking about the following feature.\n\nHave a nice day.</string>
    <string name="noUpdate">No update available</string>
    <string name="permissionRequired">Permission needed</string>
    <string name="permissionGoTo">Go to \"Permissions\" and set \"Files and media\" to \"Allow\".</string>
    <string name="updateDownload">Update is downloading.</string>
    <string name="grantPermission">This app needs permission to read your storage and write to your files. If you have doubts about privacy then read \"App Permissions\".</string>
    <string name="copiedMessage">The quote has been copied to your clipboard.</string>
    <string name="License">Licenses</string>
    <string name="licensemsg">This app uses following licenses:&lt;br/>&lt;br/> Lottie files with &lt;a href="https://lottiefiles.com/page/license">LottieFiles-License:&lt;/a> &lt;br/>According to &lt;a href="https://lottiefiles.com/">Lottie:&lt;/a> \'Use of Files without attributing the creator(s) of the Files is permitted under this license, though attribution is strongly encouraged. If attributions are included, such attributions should be visible to the end user.\'&lt;br/>I used following Lottie-Animations:&lt;br/>&lt;a href="https://lottiefiles.com/79172-update?lang=de">update (Blue loader for update)&lt;/a> by Domenico Gonnelli&lt;br/>&lt;a href="https://lottiefiles.com/82073-testimonials-icon?lang=de">Testimonials Icon (Smooth reveal icon for testimonials - web design.)&lt;/a> by Rachel Eppy&lt;br/>&lt;a href="https://lottiefiles.com/61169-no-wifi-connection-error?lang=de"> no wifi connection error (no wifi connection error animation)&lt;/a> by quang_do204</string>
    <string name="noInternetMessage">Your device currently is not connected to the internet</string>

</resources>